Mss.B.St65p
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Roney, James G., Jr., 1964
  - Roos, Charles, 1965
  - Roosa, Robert A., 1960
  - Roose, Lawrence J., 1955
  - Roosevelt, Anna Eleanor, 1954
    Mrs. Franklin D. Roosevelt.
  - Root, Albert S., 1939-1941
  - Root, Howard F., 1958
  - Root, Lin, 1961
  - Root, Maurice T., 1950, 1959
  - Root, Walter S., 1954
  - Rorem, C. Rufus, 1960
  - Ros, Arturo R., 1952
  - Rose, Ada C., 1967
  - Rose, Catharine S., 1953
  - Rose, Edward, 1947
  - Rose, Elizabeth Kirk, 1945-1969; 2.0 folders
  - Rose, John Andrew, 1940-1960; 2.0 folders
  - Rose, Noel R., 1967-1968
  - Rose, Ralph A., 1956-1957
  - Roseboro, Helen, 1971
  - Rosell, R.R., 1939, 1942
  - Rosen, Abe S., 1967, 1970
  - Rosen, Leonard S., 1957
  - Rosen, Mrs. Samuel B., 1953
  - Rosenbaum, Fanny Rose, 1953
  - Rosenbaum, Milton, 1955-1956
  - Rosenberg, Barbara, 1961
  - Rosenberg, Charles, 1950
  - Rosenberg, Dan S., 1939
  - Rosenberg, David B., 1962-1963
  - Rosenberg, James, 1965
  - Rosenberg, Margo, 1951
  - Rosenberg, Philip, 1947-1952
  - Rosenbusch, _____, 1949
  - Rosendal, Kirsten, 1970
  - Rosenfeld, Anita, 1955
  - Rosenfield, Robert L., 1971
  - Rosenn, Frank Scott, 1961
  - Rosenstern, Iwan, 1954, 1963
  - Rosenthal, Ada, 1946
  - Rosenthal, Ira M., 1961
  - Rosenthal, Nathan, 1950
  - Rosenthal, Stephen I., 1950
  - Rosenwald, Julius, II, 1962
  - Rosenwald, Lessing Julius, 1950-1971
  - Rosnov, Mitchell, 1942
  - Ross, Alan S., 1945-1960
  - Ross, Donald C., 1956-1966
  - Ross, Douglas C., Jr., 1959
  - Ross, George B., 1966
  - Ross, John E., 1962
  - Ross, S. Graham, 1944-1946
  - Rossi, E., 1952
  - Rossi, Helen, 1965
  - Rothe, Horst, 1954-1955
  - Rourke, Anthony J.J., 1953-1964
  - Roussel Corporation, 1952
  - Rowland, Lewis P., 1954-1956, 1967
  - Rowley, Samuel D., 1952, 1958
  - Rowntree, Leonard G., 1941-1959
  - Roy Bernard Company, 1952
  - Royal, Joseph S., 1955
  - Royal Typewriter Company, 1956
  - Royce, Elizabeth, 1946
  - Royster, Henry P., 1965-1967
  - Royster, Hubert A., 1946-1971
  - Royster, Lawrence T., 1941-1944
  - Rubel, Donald C., 1939-1941
  - Ruben, Alan B., 1962-1966
  - Rubenstein, Robert, 1966
  - Rubin, Emanuel, 1957-1958
  - Rubin, Mitchell I., 1941-1968; 2.0 folders
  - Rubin, Norman, 1969
  - Rubino, Rosemarie, 1951-1952
  - Rubinstein, Fannie D., 1946-1947
  - Rubinstein, Jack H., 1956
  - Rubenstein, Jacob, 1954
  - Rubright, Harold E., 1961
  - Ruch, Dorothy A., 1942
  - Rudin, Donald O., 1960
  - Rudolph, Joseph, 1946-1951
  - Rudolph, Judy, 1962
  - Ruebner, Boris, 1958
  - Rueda, Pedro, 1952
  - Ruffin, Peter B., 1967
  - Rumble, Ruth F., 1948
  - Runge, Gretchen H., 1950, 1955
  - Runge, Thomas M., 1950-1964
  - Rusch, Paul, 1955
  - Rush, Renee Carol, 1956
  - Rusk, Howard A., 1967-1969
  - Russia, 1957-1960; 2.0 folders
  - Russian War Relief, 1941-1946
  - Russo vs. Merck, 1958-1961
  - Ruthberg, Jack, 1954
  - Rutkowski, Donna, 1961
  - Rutledge, Mary Lou, 1950
  - Rutman, Irvin, 1968
  - Rutstein, David D., 1944-1963
  - Rutter, Kevin, 1961
  - Rutzky, Julius, 1959
  - Ryan, Andrew A., 1966
  - Ryan, Patricia, 1957
  - Ryan, Thomas J., 1942
  - Ryle, John A., 1947
  - Ryssing, Erik, 1950
  - Sabel, I., 1941
  - Sabin, Albert B., 1948-1968
  - Sachs, Lee Robert, 1961
  - Sacks, Lester, 1959
  - Sacks, Robert E., 1966
  - Sadusk, Joseph F., Jr., 1951
  - Sagamore, New York, 1936
  - Sagik, Bernard P., 1955
  - Sagredo, Lillian, 1954
  - Saha, Kunal, 1959
  - Saint, Eric G., 1956
  - Salcedo, Manuel, 1954
  - Salisbury, Peter F., 1950
  - Salk, Jonas E., 1949-1962
  - Salter, Lawrence C., 1952
  - Saltzman, Edward J., 1952-1964
  - Salvesen, H.A., 1951
  - Sambor, Diana, 1961
  - Sanchez, Luis Felipe, 1969-1971
  - Sandberg, George W., 1949
  - Sandberg, T.R., 1949
  - Sandoz Panorama, 1968-1969
  - Sandstrom, Walter, 1953
  - Sanford, Heyworth N., 1941
  - Sano, Ichiro, 1962
  - Sano, Machteld E., 1942
  - Sano, Tomatsu, 1956
  - Sanson, Aaron I., 1967-1968
  - Sant' Albano, Suniva de, 1961
  - Sappenfield, Robert Warren, 1952-1964
  - Sarber, Raymond W., 1960
  - Sarett, Lewis H., 1970
  - Sartwell, Philip E., 1951-1953
  - Sass-Katorsak, A., 1955-1956
  - Sataloff, Joseph, 1953, 1960
  - Satjadibrata, Kwari, 1958-1959
  - Satko, James, 1961
  - Satterthwaite, J. Ralph, 1959
  - Satterthwaite, Margaret, 1953
  - Sauer, L.W., 1948-1949
  - W.B. Saunders Company, 1941-1968
  - Sauderson, Robert W., Jr., 1961-1962
  - Savage, George M., 1942
  - Savitz, S.P., 1950
  - Sawyer, Blackwell, 1952
  - Sawyer, Henry W., III, 1954-1958
  - Sawyer, Robert K., 1951
  - Sawyer, Wilbur A., 1941
  - Saxton, Anne, 1969
  - Saxton, George A., Jr., 1961
  - Saylor, Harold D., 1969
  - Saylor, William H., 1964, 1968
  - Sayser, H. David, 1943
  - Scandiffio, M., 1941
  - Scannell, John M., 1954
  - Scatchard, George, 1949
  - Scattergood, Henry, 1941-1969
  - Scattergood, Peter, 1969
  - Scattergood, Sarah, 1966
  - Schaal, Lee Mason, 1948
  - Schade, George, 1946
  - Schaeffer, Katherine, 1938-1955
  - Schaeffer, Morris, 1951, 1966
  - Schafer, Irwin A., 1956
  - Schafer, Jonathan, 1962
  - Schafer, Walter, 1944
  - Schaffer, Lewis A., 1960
  - Schaffer, Marion, 1962
  - Schaffner, Millicent, 1946, 1955
  - Schairer, Eric, 1961
  - Scheffey, Lewis C., 1947-1961
  - Scheiderbaner, Laura, 1950
  - Scheie, Harold G., 1950-1965
  - Schenck, Harry P., 1946, 1967
  - Schermer, George, 1954
  - Scherp, Henry W., 1936-1941
  - Schick, Bela, 1941-1952
  - Schick, Marie, 1948
  - Schiff, Leon, 1951-1965
  - Schipper, Martha Taylor, 1952-1953
  - Schleifer, Marie, 1964
  - Schlesinger, Bernard, 1953, 1967
  - Schlesinger, R. Walter, 1941, 1946
  - Schless, Robert A., 1947
  - Schley, Reeve, 1946
  - Schloss, Gerd T., 1953
  - Schlumberger, Hans G., 1946
  - Schlunk, Elsie, 1967
  - Schmidt, Evelyn D., 1955
  - Schmidt, Paul J., 1962
  - Schmidt, Ralph E., 1954
  - Schmitt, Francis Q., 1968
  - Schmitt, Harry, 1961
  - Schnabel, Truman G., 1946-1964
  - Schnabel, Truman G., Jr., 1960
  - Schnall, David J., 1953-1959
  - Schneller, John J., 1948
  - Schoen, Edgar J., 1970
  - Schoettle, Mrs. Karl, 1952
  - School District of Philadelphia, 1945-1947
  - Schooley, Margaret, 1950
  - Schoonmaker, Becky, 1948-1953
  - Schoonmaker, Robert S., 1953-1966
  - Schottland, Charles I., 1956-1957
  - Schrack, W.D., Jr., 1959-1961
  - Schraeder, Gene, 1957
  - Schreiber and Osterweil, 1971
  - Schroeder, Carlton, 1960
  - Schroeder, Max J., 1951
  - Schrum, David, 1948
  - Schultz, E., 1958
  - Schultz, Herbert F., 1964-1967
  - Schumacker, Heinz, 1966
  - Schwalm, Karen, 1961
  - Schwartz, Louis, 1941
  - Schwartz, M. William, 1964
  - Schwartz, Nan, 1961
  - Schwartzman, Bernard, 1940
  - Schweidel, Seldon, 1970
  - Schwentker, Francis F., 1937-1953
  - Science, 1967
  - Science and Medicine, 1970
  - Science Service, 1964
  - Scientific American, 1953
  - Scope, 1952-1969
  - Scott, Dwight, 1954
  - Scott, Ernest, 1954
  - Scott, Hugh, 1968-1970
    Senator of Pennsylvania
  - Scott, Hugh, 1967-1968
  - Scott, Mrs. I.M., 1952-1953
  - Scott, Isadore M., 1968-1969
  - Scott, Joan, 1960
  - Scott, John Porter, 1946-1966
  - Scott, Letitia B., 1944
  - Scott, Nathan B., 1937, 1951
  - Scott, O.A., 1945
  - Scott, Philip, 1958
  - Scott, Roland B., 1948-1968
  - Scott, T.F. McNair, 1942-1972; 4.0 folders
  - Scott, William, 1946
  - Scoville, Susan T., 1970
  - Scrimshaw, Nevin S., 1951-1969
  - Scudder, John, 1952
  - Scully, Thomas J., 1968-1969
  - G. D. Searle and Company, 1962
  - Sears, Mrs. R.H., 1945
  - Sebrell, W.H., 1942
  - Sebring, Orvel, 1961
  - Secrephone, 1955-1956
  - Segal, Benjamin, 1955-1965
  - Segal, Bernard G., 1944
  - Segal, Sydney, 1962-1963
  - Segarra, Ferdinand, 1972
  - Segi, Mitsuo, 1967
  - Seiden, George, 1949
  - Seipt, Irene S., 1940-1942
  - Selecky, Medard A., 1960
  - Selfa, Jose, 1946-1947
  - Seligson, David, 1946, 1964
  - Selke, Albert, 1954-1957
  - Sellers, Alfred M., 1969
  - Sellers, Robert, 1941
  - Senecal, Jean, 1953
  - Senior, John R., 1964-1965
  - Senn, Milton J.E., 1946-1956
  - Seraphico, Luisa Rydyrier, 1953
  - Seraphico, Mario, 1952-1953
  - Setterberg, Rose, 1969
  - Setzer, Grace, 1952
  - Severens, J.M., 1959
  - Severinghaus, Elmer L., 1955
  - Seward, H., 1962-1963
  - Sewell, Edward M., 1949-1969
  - Sewell, Lemuel T., 1947
  - Sgouris, James T., 1971
  - Shaeffer, Walter, 1944
  - Shafer, John Thomas, 1961
  - Shaffer, Blanche W., 1952
  - Shaffer, Frank W., 1949-1966
  - Shaffer, James M., 1961
  - Shaffer, Morris F., 1942-1962
  - Shaffer, Thomas E., 1962
  - Shaheen, Eleanor, 1954
  - Shalit, Joseph, 1941
  - Shanahan, J. Rush, 1960
  - Shands, A.R., 1942, 1953
  - Shane, Mrs. Joseph B., 1964
  - Shannon, James A., 1965
  - Shapiro, Lawrence M., 1948
  - Shapiro, Norma, 1951
  - Shapiro, Sam, 1958
  - Shapp, Milton, 1970
  - Sharlin, David N., 1966-1971
  - Sharma, N.L., 1960
  - Sharp and Dohme, 1946-1956; 2.0 folders
  - Sharpe, William D., 1957
  - Sharples, Wynne, 1959
  - Sharpless, Frederick C., 1950
  - Sharpless, Isaac, 1954, 1957
  - Sharpless, Mr. and Mrs. T. Kite, 1941-1952
  - Sharpless, Thomas, 1942
  - Shatin, Harriet E. Sommer, 1946
  - Shaw, A.E., 1962
  - Shaw, Audrey B., 1958
  - Shaw, Dorothy R., 1938-1941
  - Shaw, Edward B., 1947-1961
  - Shaw, John I., 1953-1960
  - Sheaffer, Peter, 1953
  - Sheaffer, Mrs. Theodore, 1953-1954
  - Shelburne, Palmer A., 1948
  - Shelley, Walter B., 1955-1956
  - Shen, Jerome T.Y., 1953
  - Sheppard, William E., 1966
  - Sherbon, David, 1943
  - Sherlock, Sheila, 1952, 1962
  - Sherman, James M., 1945
  - Sherpick, William E., 1951
  - Sherr, Louis, 1946-1966
  - Sherr, Ronald H., 1969
  - Sherry, Judith A., 1968
  - Sherry, Sol, 1968
  - Sheth, S.C., 1950
  - Shewbrooks, D.M., 1940
  - Shields, John Judd, 1961
  - Shinn, Lester, 1961
  - Shinn, Susan, 1961
  - Shinn, Virginia, 1961
  - Shipley, Elizabeth, 1971
  - Shipley, Morris S., 1964-1965
  - Shipley, Thomas E., Jr., 1970
  - Shipley, Mr. and Mrs. Walter P., 1968
  - Shipp, Velma D., 1956
  - Shippen, Katherine, 1947
  - Shippen, Nelly, 1957
  - Shipps, H.P., 1941
  - Shirkey, Harry C., 1962
  - Shissler, Ronald H., 1957
  - Shoemaker, Elizabeth Lowry, 1940
  - Shoemaker, Robert, 1953
  - Shope, Helen, 1945
  - Shope, Richard E., 1937-1961; 2.0 folders
  - Shore, Jeffrey, 1961
  - Shorey, Jeannette McConnell, 1952, 1954
  - Short, Joan Kalaine, 1960-1962
  - Shortlidge, Elizabeth N., 1950
  - Shrack, W.D., 1950
  - Shrigley, E.W., 1953
  - Shryock, Richard Harrison, 1957, 1962
  - Shull, G.M., 1965
  - Shuman, H.H., 1947
  - Shuman, Vilda, 1941-1948
  - Sibinga, Maarten S., 1959-1962
  - Sibley, Hiram, 1962
  - Sidbury, J. Buren, 1939-1961
  - Siegel, Abraham L., 1946
  - Siegel, Leo H., 1951
  - Siegel, Mrs. Sidney L., 1947
  - Siegfried, John D., 1959, 1962
  - Sigel, M. Michael, 1946-1959
  - Sigman, Cheney C., 1951
  - Sigmond, Robert, 1962-1970
  - Siim, Jorgen, 1950-1971; 2.0 folders
  - Silirie, C. Paul, 1959
  - Silva, Tomas Gomez Maganda, 1953
  - Silver, Henry K., 1943-1969; 2.0 folders
  - Silver, John A., 1960
  - Silver, Morris A., 1944
  - Silver Spur Ranch School, 1947
  - Silverberg, Minor D., 1950
  - Silverblatt, Florence, 1965
  - Silverschmidt, Marianne, 1950
  - Silverson, Leonard, 1968
  - Silverstein, David J., 1948
  - Silverthorne, Nelles, 1949-1955
  - Simmel, Else, 1923, 1940
  - Simmons, Donald R., 1950
  - Simmons, James Stevens, 1942-1951
  - Simmons, Vaughan P., 1949, 1962
  - Simms, Deborah, 1961
  - Simon, Erich H.W., 1967
  - Simon, Mary, 1966
  - Simon, Thomas, 1957
  - Simpson, Charles, 1970
  - Sims, Eric B., 1959
  - Sinclair, Sydney E., 1950
  - Singer, Samuel, 1963
  - Singh, Inder, 1956
  - Sinkler, Louise E., 1947, 1966
  - Siracusa, Mary, 1952
  - Sirlin, Edward M., 1939-1964
  - Sisson, Warren R., 1942, 1959
  - Sitkoff, Malcolm, 1971
  - Skillman, Stephen, 1961
  - Skillman State School, 1952-1954
  - Skytop Lodge, 1940-1942
  - Slaughter, Bennie Celia, 1949-1952
  - Slingerland, Stuart W., 1961
  - Slingluff, Ella, 1961
  - Sloan, Judge Joseph, 1939
  - Sloan, Joseph M., 1956, 1968
  - Slocum, Richard, 1953
  - Slovis, Thomas, 1967
  - Smadel, Joseph E., 1948-1963
  - Smalley, Ruth E., 1962
  - Smellie, Jean M., 1959
  - Smellow, Mrs. Benjamin, 1970-1972
  - Smetana, Hans F., 1953
  - Smiley, James L., 1961-1962
  - Smillie, W.G., 1944
  - Smith, Austin, 1958
  - Smith, Brainard S., 1956
  - Smith, Clarence N., 1949
  - Smith, Clement A., 1942-1955
  - Smith, Courtney, 1966
  - Smith, D.C. Wharton, 1938-1952
  - Smith, De Lesesne, Jr., 1942
  - Smith, Edward A., 1946
  - Smith, Edward B., 1948
  - Smith, Edward B., Jr., 1951-1953
  - Smith, Eleanor H., Undated
  - Smith, Forrest M., 1953
  - Smith, Frank W., 1945
  - Smith, Grace S., 1936
  - Smith, Homer, 1945
  - Smith, Hugo Dunlop, 1949, 1962
  - Smith, Lauren H., 1941
  - Smith, Lawrence M.C., 1941-1970
  - Smith, Lloyd H., 1967
  - Smith, M. Margaret, 1951
  - Smith, Margaret, 1957
  - Smith, Margaret Chase, 1957
  - Smith, Margaret H.D., 1945-1969
  - Smith, Martin H., 1947
  - Smith, Nathan J., 1957-1966
  - Smith, R. Lawrence, 1946-1948
  - Smith, Richard M., 1945-1946
  - Smith, Richard T., 1958-1959
  - Smith, Robert C., 1966, 1968
  - Smith, Robert R., 1940
  - Roger Smith Hotel
  - Smith, Roy M., 1944-1969
  - Smith, Stewart P., 1964
  - Smith, William H., 1949-1950
  - Smith-Vickers, Evelyn, 1940
  - Smolens, Joseph, 1943-1950
  - Smorodintsev, A.A., 1967
  - Smyers, Scott, 1961
  - Smyth, Francis Scott, 1939-1967; 2.0 folders
  - Smythe, Ruth, 1940
  - Snedeker, Lendon, 1941-1963
  - Snell, Albert M., 1946-1947
  - Snelling, C.E., 1948
  - Snoke, Albert W., 1946-1963
  - Snow, Spencer, 1955, 1959
  - Snyder, C. Harrison, 1943-1953
  - Snyder, Caroline M., 1940, 1942
  - Snyder, Eleanor N., 1954, 1956
  - Snyder, Mrs. G., 1956
  - Snyder, James D., 1961
  - Snyder, Miriam Lieber, 1955
  - Snyderman, Selma E., 1944
  - Snydman, Leonard, 1942
  - Soban, William A., 1950
  - Soble, A.B., 1967
  - Social Security Bill, 1935
  - Soedarman, Iskaq Darsono, 1961
  - Soetojo, Raden, 1963
  - Sohn, William J., 1953-1961
  - Solenberger, Edith Reeves, 1963-1965
  - Solomon, Irwin, 1962
  - Soloviev, Valentin, 1966-1971
  - Soman, D.W., 1950-1951
  - Somers, Anne R., 1961-1971; 8.0 folders
  - Somers, Herman M., 1965
  - Sommer, George N.J., 1956
  - Sommer, Harriet, 1942-1943
  - Sommers, Martin, 1956
  - Sonder, M.J., 1958
  - Sonis, Meyer, 1953-1969; 2.0 folders
  - Sontag, L.W., 1960
  - Soper, Dr., 1950
  - Sorr, Edward Mark, 1965-1967
  - Sotelo, Luis, 1953-1954
  - Soto, Carlos, 1961
  - Soto, Emilio, 1960-1967
  - Soto, Ignacio, Jr., 1958
  - Southard, Samuel C., 1956
  - Southbury Training School, 1947
  - Souther, George, 1961
  - Southern Medicine and Surgery, 1952
  - Soutter, Lamar, 1948
  - Sozer, ____, 1959
  - Spaeth, Edmund B., Jr., 1966-1967
  - Spahr, Mary B., 1947
  - Spahr, Richard R., 1955
  - Spanel, Abraham Nathaniel, 1960-1970
  - Sparks, David, Jr., 1962
  - Spaulding, Mary G., 1949
  - Spear, Olga H., 1954
  - Specht, Heinz, 1970
  - Specter, Samuel, 1950-1951
  - Speer, Bernhard, 1964
  - Speer, Holly, 1940-1954
  - Spence, Sir James, 1949-1950
  - Spencer, David, 1961
  - Spencer, Mrs. Merle, 1955
  - Spencer, Rowena, 1949-1950
  - Spencer, Steven M., 1947-1954
  - Sperber, Zanwil, 1960
  - Spiegleman, Marvin H., 1947
  - Spies, Tom D., 1950
  - Spikes, Marjorie D., 1945
  - Spink, Wesley W., 1944, 1951
  - Spitz, Eugene B., 1949-1961
  - Spock, Benjamin, 1965
  - Sporn, Jay, 1954
  - Sproles, John, 1961
  - Spruance, Peter B., 1963-1967
  - Sprunt, Katherine, 1948
  - Spur, Bernhard, 1958
  - E.R. Squibb and Sons, 1957
  - Srouji, Elias, 1946-1960
  - Stackhouse, Mary L., 1946
  - Stadie, William C., 1946-1968
  - Staehle, George E., 1947
  - Stafford, Doreen, 1954
  - Stafford, Jane, 1951
  - Stafford, John, 1954
  - Stafford, John L., 1956, 1960
  - Stahl, Lawrence, 1953
  - Stahle, D.C., 1944
  - A.E. Staley Manufacturing Company, 1943, 1945
  - Stamler, Jeremiah, 1965-1971
  - Standard Adjustment Agency, 1954
  - Stanford, W.R., 1944-1947
  - Staniszewski, Herbert, 1952
  - Stanley, N.F., 1954
  - Stanley, Wendall M., 1955-1956, 1971
  - Starkweather, George, 1950
  - Starr, Harold J., 1950
  - Starr, Isaac, 1942-1971
  - State Civil Service Commission, 1953-1954
  - Stavitsky, Abram B., 1946-1947
  - Stearns, Frederic R., 1950
  - Frederick Stearns and Company, 1941
  - Steele, Mark W., 1962
  - Steen, R.E., 1968
  - Steer, John W., 1946
  - Steffens, Ralph, 1940
  - Steiger, Howard P., 1950
  - Steigerwalt, John Latshaw, 1946-1956
  - Steigman, Alex J., 1945-1970; 2.0 folders
  - Steigman, William F., 1957-1958
  - Steiker, D.D., 1961
  - Stein, Eleanor Robb, 1940
  - Stein, H.N., 1939
  - Stein, Linda, 1967
  - Stein, Marvin, 1960
  - Stein, Philip, 1943, 1948
  - Stein, Stuart, 1969
  - Steinberg, Arthur G., 1959
  - Steinberg, Marvin E., 1968
  - Stelle, Robert M., 1964-1971
  - Stephenson, Charles S., 1951, 1953
  - Stephenson, Mary V., 1940
  - Stephenson, William G., 1969
  - Sterbenz, Francis J., 1962
  - Stern, Curt, 1933
  - Stern, Kurt, 1953-1954
  - Stern, Lee D., 1941
  - Sterne, Mrs. Charles, Jr., 1966
  - Sterner, John A., 1948-1949
  - Stetten, DeWitt, Jr., 1968-1970
  - Stevens, Mrs. C. Laurence, 1961
  - Stevens, David, 1941-1946
  - Stevens, Harold, 1940-1942
  - Stevens, John E., 1947
  - Stevens, Lewis M., 1950
  - Stevens, Richard K., 1945-1971
  - Stevenson, Adlai, 1954
  - Stevenson, Arthur, Undated
  - Stevenson, Frank E., 1944
  - Stevenson, Stuart S., 1949-1958
  - Stevenson, William J., 1961-1962
  - Stewart, Chester A., 1941-1944
  - Stewart, Ellen, 1956
  - Stewart, James B., 1940
  - Stewart, Margaret, 1941
  - Stewart, Sloan G., 1946
  - Stewart, Walter B., 1945-1969
  - Stewart, William H., 1962-1966
  - Stickney, David, 1940
  - Still, Joseph W., 1946-1970
  - Still, William J.S., 1956-1958
  - Stilson, Carter, 1954
  - Stimson, Philip M., 1940-1958
  - Stinnes, Edmund H., 1949-1951
  - Stinson, Harriet, 1967
  - Stithe, Jessie, 1941
  - Stitzel, Elwood W., 1939-1952
  - Stockner, James, 1961
  - Stockwell, John F., 1964
  - Stoddard, Alexander J., 1942-1943
  - Stokes, Allen, 1952
  - Stokes, Ann Fannin, 1948
  - Stokes, Anne, 1961
  - Stokes, Donald, 1945-1957
  - Stokes, Eleanor, 1954-1962
  - Stokes, Emlen, 1942-1944
  - Stokes, F. Joseph, Jr., 1959-1966
  - Stokes, Francis J., 1943-1955
  - Stokes, Harmena, 1950
  - Stokes, J.F., 1958
  - Stokes, J.S., 1948
  - Stokes, J. Tyson, 1966
  - Stokes, J. Warrington, 1946
  - Stokes, James M., 1963
  - Stokes, John, 1958-1965
  - Stokes, John B., Jr., 1947-1966
  - Stokes, John B., III, 1966
  - Stokes, John H., 1940-1957; 2.0 folders
  - Stokes, John Stogdale, 1945
  - Stokes, Joseph, Sr., 1949
  - Stokes, Joseph, III, 1954-1961
  - Stokes, Lelia, 1958, 1964
  - Stokes, Lydia, 1958
  - Stokes, May, 1952-1964
  - Stokes, Peter, 1966
  - Stokes, Ruth, 1966
  - Stokes, S. Emlen, 1947-1955
  - Stokes, Samuel E., 1954
  - Stokes, William, 1967
  - Stone, Alice W., 1951
  - Stone, E. Franklin, Jr., 1960
  - Stone, Suzanne M., 1956-1957
  - Stone, William S., 1946, 1954
  - Stopford, Sir John, 1946
  - Storer, Leonard J., 1947
  - Stork Diaper Service, 1944
  - Stouffer, John W., 1967
  - Stovall, W.D., 1963
  - Stover, J.H., 1949
  - Stratton-Michener, Sina, 1943
  - Straub, W.F., 1949
  - Strauss, Elias, 1950
  - Strauss, Hyman, 1954
  - Strawbridge, George, 1952
  - Strayhorn, David, 1953
  - Strecker, Edward A., 1942-1956
  - Street, Edward P., 1945-1948
  - Strenge, Henry B., 1951
  - Strode, George K., 1941-1954
  - Stroeder, J., 1967-1968
  - Strohschein, Ruth Kraft, 1955
  - Strong, Laurence E., 1948
  - Strong, Paul S., 1952
  - Strong, Paul T., 1948
  - Strong, Robert A., 1941-1944
  - Stroud, Henry H., 1965-1969
  - Stroud, William D., 1941-1952
  - Stroup, Chalmers, 1968
  - Strumia, Max M., 1945
  - Struthers, R.R., 1961
  - Stryker, Winfield, 1952
  - Stuart, Harold C., 1940-1949
  - Stuart-Harris, C.H., 1953-1966
  - Stubblefield, Robert L., 1952
  - Stunkard, Albert J., 1962-1971
  - Sturgis, Katharine Boucot, 1970
  - Sturgis, Katharine R., 1969
  - Stutman, Leonard J., 1958
  - Su, T.F., 1948
  - Suarez, Mrs. Robert, Jr., 1962
  - Sugg, John Y., 1952
  - Sullivan, Daniel F., 1961
  - Sullivan, Eugene R., 1948
  - Sullivan, Leon, 1967-1968
  - Sumen, Ali F., 1952
  - Summey, Thomas J., 1953
  - Sunderman, F. William, 1946
  - Supplee, F.N.P., 1946
  - Supplee, Henderson, Jr., 1940-1943
  - Surgenor, Douglas, 1963-1969
  - Sussman, Walter, 1948, 1952
  - Sutherland, Allan, 1939
  - Sutter, Everett C., 1965
  - Sutton, Lee E., Jr., 1941
  - Sutton, R.N.P., 1968
  - Sveda, Michael, 1952-1955, 1970
  - Swager, Thelma, 1940
  - Swan, Martha C.A., 1947
  - Swanson, B.E., 1955
  - Swartz, Donald R., 1964
  - Swayne, Noah, 1935
  - Sweet, Clifford, 1954
  - Sweigard, Charles B., 1957-1961
  - Swertloff, Harry, 1948
  - Swezey, Robert L., 1959
  - Swihart, John J., 1950
  - Sylverton, Jerome T., 1950-1956
  - Synopsis of Pediatrics, 1963
  - Szanton, Jules, 1964-1965
  - Szanton, Peter L., 1959, 1971
  - Szilard, Leo, 1955
  - Taber, Robert Clarke, 1941-1958
  - Tabet, George, 1958
  - Takahashi, William Y., 1944-1945
  - Takatsu, Tadao, 1957-1958
  - Talbot, Nathan B., 1942-1971; 2.0 folders
  - Talbot, Mrs. William R., 1959
  - Talbott, John H., 1964
  - Taliaferro, W.H., 1960
  - Talk Philadelphia, 1940
  - Tall, Milton G., 1956-1958
  - Talner, Norman, 1966
  - Tamboli, Vito F., 1964-1965
  - Tan, Charlotte T.C., 1951-1955
  - Tang, I. Ling, 1945
  - Tappan, Vivian, 1946-1959
  - Tate, James H., 1966-1970
    Mayor of Philadelphia
  - Taussig, Helen B., 1947-1962
  - Taussig, Sue, 1944
  - Taxin, John, 1967
  - Tayloe, David T., 1951, 1959
  - Tayloe, Gordon B., 1943
  - Taylor, Carl E., 1952
  - Taylor, Frederick R., 1951
  - Taylor, G.W., 1949
  - Taylor, Herbert W., 1941
  - Taylor, Howard C., Jr., 1958-1959
  - Taylor, Marjorie F., Undated
  - Taylor, Paul M., 1953-1954
  - Taylor, Rebecca, 1943
  - Taylor, Roland, 1942
  - Taylor, W.J. Russell, 1971
  - Taylor and Atmore, 1953
  - Te, Ay-King, and Ramon, 1960-1962
  - Teague, Russell E., 1958
  - Teate, H. Luten, Jr., 1952, 1961
  - Teichmann, ______, 1962
  - Television Production Engineering Corporation, 1959
  - Tenney, S. Marsh, 1960
  - Tepper, Warren R., 1955
  - Terrell, John Sandford, 1961-1962
  - Terris, Milton, 1954
  - Terry, Luther L., 1965-1971
  - Test, Daniel D., 1962-1963
  - Tezck, Omar Fethi, 1951
  - Thaler, Heribert L., 1954, 1958
  - Thalheimer, Edward J., 1959
  - Thalhimer, William, 1942-1950
  - Thelander, H.E., 1971
  - Thenebar, C.L., 1949
  - Thimmegowda, Chamegowda, 1961
  - This Week magazine, 1962
  - Thode, Nancy C., 1966-1967
  - Thogmartin, Bruce M., 1966
  - Thomaidis, Theodore S., 1959
  - Thomas, Carol, 1955
  - Thomas, Charles C., 1941-1951
  - Thomas, Dudley R., 1956
  - Thomas, H.M., Jr., 1949-1950
  - Thomas, Howard P., Jr., 1957-1959
  - Thompkins, Charles A., 1947
  - Thompkins, Pendleton, 1944-1946
  - Thompkins, Winslow T., 1948-1949
  - Thompson, Charles M., 1956
  - Thompson, David I., 1952-1962
  - Thompson, George R., 1969
  - Thompson, Randall L., 1947
  - Thompson, W.T., Jr., 1959-1961
  - Thomson, Edgar, 1951
  - Thorling, Leif, 1950-1951
  - Thorn, George, 1965
  - Thorne, Charles Greenwood, Jr., 1964, 1971
  - Thorp, Mrs. Francis Q., Undated
  - Thorpe, Edward S., 1948-1949
  - Thorpe, Tilman Ramsey, 1962
  - Thresher, Oliver S., 1946
  - Tibrewala, N.S., 1968
  - Tierkel, Ernest S., 1962
  - Tietze, Christopher, 1964
  - Tiffany, Elberton J., 1948
  - Time Magazine, 1946-1954
  - Timokov, _____, Undated
  - Ting, Rosalind Y., 1961
  - Tisdall, Frederick F., 1945-1948
  - Tisher, Max, 1970
  - Tizard, J.P.M., 1956
  - Tobin, Mrs. Edgar, 1955
  - Tobin, John Dudley, 1947